SYED ASIM SHAH

MERN STACK DEVELOPER

syedaasimshah1@gmail.com | https://aasimshah.site



Mardan, KP



aasimshah.site



+923179936737



syedaasimshah1@gmail.com



linkedin/aasim-shah-980113212/

PROFILE

I am a Experienced and professional web developer with three years of experience in developing full stack websites along with deployments and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

SKILLS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- ReactJs
- NextJs
- TailwindCss
- Bootstrap
- Html/css/Js
- Firebase

• BACK-END DEVELOPER

- Nodeis
- Mongodb
- Php
- Mysql
- RestApi
- Firebase

EDUCATION

F.SC

Quaid-e-azam collage 2017-2019

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Peshawer 2019-23

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH FLUENT
- URDU NATIVE
- PASHTO NATIVE

EXPERIENCE

SOOZ MARKETPLACE

kenya based finetech company

2021 - Present

- full stack developer and website design
- Built the logic for a complete site in nodejs, mongodb
- · Done with alot of forntend techs and designing.

FREELANCING

Fiver

2021 - Present

- Full stack web development
- Deployment to cloud services
- Awesome UI